360cities.net 2013-10-31

# Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. 

##  (1) What information do we collect? 

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data: 

  * 1\. information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit, number of page views and searches you make);
  * 2\. information relating to any transactions carried out in this website, or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases or requests you make of third party's goods or services using this website; and
  * 3\. location data used to assign a location to images created by users of 360Cities mobile apps, and to display nearby images. Users can disable location services in the mobile app settings.
  * 4\. any other information that you choose to send to us.

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

##  (2) Cookies 

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and keep you logged in. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; remember your preferred language; store the city that you were last interested in. 

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date. 

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>. 

Our advertisers and/or payment services providers may also send you cookies. 

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites. 

##  (3) Using your personal data 

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. 

We may use your personal information to: 

  * 1\. administer the website;
  * 2\. improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
  * 3\. enable your use of the services available on the website;
  * 4\. send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
  * 5\. send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
  * 6\. provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user; and
  * 7\. deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us. 

We will not provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing. 

All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, Paypal. You should only provide your personal information to Paypal after reviewing the Paypal privacy policy (available at www.paypal.com). We will share information with Paypal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website. 

##  (4) Disclosures 

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers, collaborators, customers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy. 

In addition, we may disclose information about you: 

  * 1\. to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
  * 2\. in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
  * 3\. in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
  * 4\. to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties. 

##  (5) International data transfers 

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA. 

In addition, information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world. 

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information. 

##  (6) Security of your personal data 

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password protected) servers. 

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. 

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password. 

##  (7) Policy amendments 

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

##  (8) Your rights 

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. 

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.) 

##  (9) Third party websites 

The website contains links to other websites, and, upon your request, transmit your information to third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. 

##  (10) Updating information 

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. 

##  (11) Editing your account 

You can edit your 360Cities account, information and preferences at any time. New categories of marketing communications might be added to the preferences page from time to time. You can delete your 360Cities account at any time. 

##  (12) Contact 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to info@360cities.com. 

* * *

This privacy policy is based on a template created by [Template-contracts.co.uk](http://template-contracts.co.uk/) and distributed by [http://www.website-law.co.uk](http://www.website-law.co.uk/).
